Priyanka Kushwaha

Java Full Stack Developer

Meticulous Web developer, specialized in frontend/backend development for complex scalable web apps, passion for responsive website design and firm believer in mobile-first approach. and also Founder of Cloud9DIYs, Creative and motivated Executive with experience in overseeing daily business activities and improving overall business functions.



Work History

2017-01 -2021-01

Creative and Motivated Executive

Cloud9DIYs, Gurgaon

Creative and motivated Executive with experience in overseeing daily business activities and improving overall business functions, Strong decision maker and good client relationship builder. Proven capacity to multi-task and utilize time management and conflict resolution skills to increase efficiencies. Positive attitude with proven leadership skills and the ability to develop successful team environment.

2014-08 -2015-02

Project Trainee

Benchmark IT Solution, Pune

- Troubleshot and debugged code ensuring compatibility with devices, browsers and operating systems.
- Developed user interfaces with modern JavaScript frameworks, HTML5 and CSS3.
- Adapted quickly to constantly changing, deadline-driven environment.
- Worked closely with developers on creating new code.



Education

2009-09 -2013-06

Bachelor of Science: Computer Science Engineering

Bansal Institute of Science and Technology - Bhopal



Contact

Address

Austin, United State 78758

Phone

+1 512 203 9286

E-mail

priyankakushwaha0702@ gmail.com

Work Permit

US L2 Visa



HTML5

Excellent

CSS3

Very Good

JavaScript

Very Good

Responsive Design & Mobile-First Website

Very Good

Core Java

Good



Good

2022-05 CSS

2022-05 HTML5

2023-06 JavaScript

2023-06 Java



Art

Dancing

Listening to music

Travel